<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-02-23T20:03:19+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReginaldS</title><subtitle>This is my amazing page</subtitle><author><name>ReginaldS.</name></author><entry><title type="html">Thanks 2022 you are good refections years</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/_pages/post/Thanks-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thanks 2022 you are good refections years" /><published>2022-02-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-02-23T07:22:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/_pages/post/Thanks-2022</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/_pages/post/Thanks-2022/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/images/image-2022-reflections.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;” You do not love yourself enough. Or No great thing is you would love your nature too, and what it demands of you. “&lt;/strong&gt;
~ &lt;em&gt;Marcus Aurelius&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is a two-day. Today I have been living on earth for almost 9338 days already. In 2022, I can say it is my awful year and my beautiful year. I have lost myself for so many years, and this year I was found. This January, I was in bed with depression and anxiety. 
I wonder what I have been doing wrong in life. One month passed, I diagnosed myself have ADHD. Thanks to Jessica McCabe was in TedX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;853&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JiwZQNYlGQI&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She shared her experience with ADHD. That allows me to know I am not alone who suffering from that experience. I have done something that is not good for my inner-self. It makes me feel ashamed, guilty, sad, and depressed. I thought maybe I was a broken person. After I was diagnosed with that disorder, I felt more relief. I am not a fraud or loser. I can be myself that have neurodiversity. I should love and be proud of myself that I represent as a human. My skill can help humanity. What I should do is do what I can. Why do I need to be put pressure on myself to be someone that I can not be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I decided to say NO to something I am not want to do.
Careful to say Yes to something to someone. For my sake and the others. I should be a happy person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/assets/images/say-no.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So grateful that I have great people as friends and advisors. Thanks to friends and family that support me and give me time and space. Without it, I can not have time to do self-reflection and fall too deep into a rabbit hole. Or, keep it in a loop. Once &lt;em&gt;Lao Tzu&lt;/em&gt; said, &lt;strong&gt;“When you are content to be simply yourself and do not compare or compete, everyone will respect you.”&lt;/strong&gt; Appreciate Everyone’s life and yours.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>ReginaldS.</name></author><category term="_pages" /><category term="post" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>